Ian.
Okay, I'm trying to link.
It's not really working. Is the link not working? What about the QR code? I'll try the QR code instead, then.
Did I write wrong?
I mean, it's not HTTPS, so it might be that you… It's supposed to be XP, I think, or Expo.
Oh, did I not… Oh, maybe. Try the… try the QR code, let's see how that works.
The QR code… The instructions are, not there right now for, how to deploy, so I'm blaming this… Oh, no, it works okay.
This is development menu. It gives you access to useful tools in ExpoGo. That's the Expo, that's like the Expo pop-up.
But… How many guests? --
Whoa.
Very cool.
Whoa, you can click on the recipes, and you see an image.
The price? Price for 11 guests.
Ingredients…
Instructions, more info. Oh, okay, that's a link to the website. Very cool.
Add to menu…
The cancel button does not work.
They never gave us anything for the cancel button to do.
Okay. Add to menu, I guess that doesn't work when it's already in there.
Slow-cooked beef stew, that looks nice.
That's amazing. Oh, it takes you, it takes you back. That's nice.
Whoa.
Slow-cooked beef stew is way more expensive than the Tuscan white bean soup with olive oil and rosemary.
The summaries, summaries of all the ingredients.
Or both, I guess, right?
Yeah, for both dishes.
What details?
Sorry, that's gonna be awkward for the recording, huh?
This detail's the one that you were in there most recently? It is.
That's pretty cool.
Only main course, only desserts.
Yeah Is there… is there anything I should be trying to do?
I think,
You've, you've looked around a little bit. Is there any, usability problems you're finding in the app?
No, I mean…
I don't know if there is a way to get back to the home menu without using the back button.
Isn't there on the bottom? Oh, yeah, there is on the bottom.
I guess, yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, the cancel button is a bit awkward, but I think outside of that, it's pretty funny. But that's required, yeah, that's fair.
So, what would you want there to be? Do you want me to just remove the cancel button, if you were to…
Yeah, I think… I think make it a home button.
Otherwise, to be like, because… Four seats are out to home?
Yeah, because it's like, if it… I assume it's gonna route you to home, no? Like… I feel like it should route you to search.
Maybe.
Does that make sense? Yeah.
Do you have any other suggestions?
No… I don't know.
the summary list… Might be… I don't.
If there's a way to make it more clear that it's, like, total ingredients or something.
Because your summary is like… Yep.
I don't know.
At first, you're like, what, what, what do you want to call it? Shopping list?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Or, like, ingredients. I just have it, like…
When you click on the ingredients tab, you see for all ingredients, or, like, ingredients for all dishes.
Listening to… clarify it a bit. Are there other features you would want me to add?
I don't know, could maybe be nice to have for the summary part, that you can,
Increase the amount of servings as well, or the amount of guests.
Because then you… I feel like… because if you're looking at home, you can see the prices of stuff.
And then in the summary, you can see the ingredients.
Very interesting, yeah. Yeah.
You should also maybe include some kind of currency next to the…
the price is $49.70, what? Like, is it crowns? Dollars?
Very interesting.
Yeah?
I don't know, that just feels good.
Yeah, thank you.
Great, great meeting, Makam.
Great, thank you. I will… I will now stop recording.